>> Kyle Simpson: 因此，请再次跟随该幻灯片上的代码。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So again,
follow along with that code on the slide.
我要给你打个电话然后按线路连线
And I'm gonna be diagramming it for
you and we're gonna go line by line and
创建实体。
create the entities.
在我们走第一条路之前
Before we even get to line one,
我们得谈谈零线的情况，换句话说，
we need to diagram a bit about what's
happening in line zero, in other words,
在你的节目开始运作之前发生了什么
what's happening before your
program has even started to run.
在这个图中我要用一个非常简单的符号
And in this diagramming I'm gonna use
a very simple notation which is I'm gonna
使用正方形来表示对象和圆形或
use squares to represent objects and
circles or
无论我能近似的是什么功能
whatever I can approximate
thereof to represent functions.
我是用 trackpad 画的
I am drawing with a trackpad so
请原谅我的艺术作品的品质
it's not gonna be great drawing please
forgive the quality of my artwork.
我要先图的是零环境我要做的是
I'm going to diagram first the lines
zero environment i'm going to do that by
在这里画一条线基本上说这条线上面的所有东西都是
drawing a line across here that basically
says everything above this line is
零线环境，下面是我们规划程序的地方。
the line zero environment, and then below
it is where we'll diagram the program.
在我们的零环境中
Above this line in our
line zero environment,
有一个非常关键的实体
there's one very critical entity.
它是一个功能，所以我就把它画成一个近似圆的
It is a function, so I will draw
it as approximately a circle and
它是由一个非常熟悉的名字命名的，它的名字叫资本 O，对象。
it goes by a pretty familiar name,
it goes by the name capital O, object.
>> Kyle Simpson: 我只会缩写 cuz 我不喜欢写
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And I'm just gonna
abbreviate cuz I don't like writing out
这整个词都叫对象资本 O 对象
this whole words, but
it's called object, capital O object and
那是一种存在的功能
that's a function that exists.
你们都看到那是我们的基本目标之一
And you all have seen that that's
one of our fundamental objects
这种语言很可能是最重要的语言之一
that's built into the language, probably
one of the most important of those.
我们在那里有资本 O 物体，顺便说，它有几件东西。
We have capital O object there, and
by the way, it has several things on it.
它有 object.keys 和 object.values 以及其他各种实用程序。
It's got object.keys and object.values,
and various other utilities.
所以这不仅仅是一个功能
So it's not only a function, but
它还充当名称空间，以便在它上具有其他方法。
it also serves as a namespace
to have other methods on it.
因此我们使用了很多非常重要的通用实用程序
So there are a bunch of really
important general utilities that we use
通过 JavaScript 直接位于该功能上。
across JavaScript, that are located
directly on that function.
但还有一个实体存在，它是一个正方形。
But there's another entity that exists and
it is a square.
所以我在这里画一个正方形，像一个正方形。
So I will draw a square here,
something like a square.
它可能是所有 JavaScript中最重要的对象。
And it is probably the most important
object in all of JavaScript.
很重要的是我们连名字都没有
It's so important in fact that we
don't even have a name for it.
我们不能为它找个好名字
We can't come up with a good name for it.
所以你知道我们是如何命名的，我们的名字是指什么地方。
So you know how we name it, is we name
it referring to what points at it.
对象函数中有一个属性
There's a property on
the object function that points
在这个东西上，这个属性叫做雏形。
over at this thing and
that property is called prototype.
这里的写作真的很痛苦
Writing is really painful here.
我只是用缩写来写
I'm just gonna abbreviate with proto here.
这叫原型机
It's called prototype.
这是该属性的名称。
That is the name of that property.
所以如果你见过 object.prototype ，那就是指
So if you've ever seen object.prototype,
that's the property pointing from
对象函数被称为 object.prototype。
the object function over to this
thing called object.prototype.
有一堆很重要的东西在物化原型上
And there's a bunch of really
important stuff on object.prototype,
如 toString， and valueOf ， and
like toString, and valueOf, and
所有这些都存在于我们语言中的基本实用程序
all these other fundamental utilities
that exist in our language.
所有非原语直接从该 object.prototype 下降，因此
All non-primitives descend directly
from this object.prototype, so
它是一个非常重要的物体
it's a really important object.
>> Kyle Simpson: 我们的零环境中存在另一个存在的问题
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: There is one other thing
that exists in our line zero environment
就是一个指向另一个方向的财产
which is a property that's
pointing back the other direction.
这里指的是这里
It's pointing from here over to here and
他们选择了一个真正令人费解和令人沮丧的名字
that property they chose a really
perplexing and frustrating name for.
他们选择特定名称，因为他们试图做的本质上是谎言
They choose a specific name because what
they were trying to do was essentially lie
就像 JavaScript 系统有类一样
to you, to pretend as if
JavaScript system had classes so
他们选择命名此构造函数。
they choose to name this constructor.
我要写 C-o-n 的缩写
And I'm just going to
write c-o-n to abbreviate.
这叫构造函数
It's called constructor.
因此，您有此对象原型，它指向此对象，并且
So you have this object.prototype
which points at this object, and
如果你有那个物体然后说这个 .
if you had that object and
then said .constructor,
它会指向这个对象函数，就像对象
it'd be pointing back at this
object function as if the object
函数是指向它的对象的构造函数。
function was the constructor of
the object that pointed to it.
但基本原型中的工作构造函数
But that work constructor in
the fundamental prototype
系统的含义并不比 " fifar" 一词更有意义。
system has no more meaning
than the word fubar.
除了说服你之外
Other than to convince you,
这是一个类系统，因为它有构造函数，我们会看到一些
that this is a class system because it has
constructors in it and we will see a bit
后来这就是构造函数基本上是这样做的
later that's what constructor
basically comes in and pretends it,
如果你愿意的话它会帮助你的建筑我们正在处理一个阶级制度
it helps the artifice if you will,
that we are dealing with a class system.
所以我们的零线环境
So that our line zero environment.
现在我要用同样的符号重新开始 diagring
Now I'm gonna start diagraming
again with the same notation but
我要从第一条开始
I'm gonna start with line one.
第一条我们有一个工作坊的功能
On line one, we have a workshop function,
我要画一个圆圈叫做工作坊
do I'm gonna draw a circle and
it's called workshop.
但我只会为工作坊缩略词
But I'm just gonna abbreviate w for
workshop.
这就是第一个存在的功能。
That's the function that
exists on line one.
但也有第一个存在的，不明显的，
But also what exists on line one,
that is not obvious,
是由于第二行的结果而创建的另一个对象。
is that there is another object that has
been created as a result of line one and
这个物体也很重要。
that object is also pretty important.
现在是空的但这会起到非常重要的作用
At the moment it's empty but it's
gonna serve a pretty important purpose
但重要的是我们没有好的名字
except it's so important that we
don't have a good name for it.
所以我们用它的属性来引用它。
And so we refer to it by
the property that points at it.
我打赌你能猜到那房产叫什么
And I bet you can guess what
that property's called?
这个产业被称为 proto，原型机，好吗 ?
That property's called proto,
prototype, okay?
>> Kyle Simpson: 我可能正在使用文本工具，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: I could
probably be using the text tool,
但我不想在工具间切换
but I just didn't wanna mess around
with switching between tools.
这就是所谓的雏形。
So that's called prototype.
因此，我们将该对象称为 workshop.prototype，
So we refer to that object
as workshop.prototype,
这就是您在第四行 workshop.prototype上看到的内容。
which is what you see on line four,
workshop.prototype.
这是个诡异的词比如样机都是从哪里来的
It's a bizarrely named word like
where does prototype even come from?
我尝试在计算机科学中寻找原型的起源
I've tried to search for the origins of
prototype within computer science, and
它是一个模糊的 etymology
it's a murky etymology at best.
我查不到我们为什么要用这个词原型
I can't come up with why we
use this word prototype or
这都是什么意思
what it's even supposed to mean.
但这条线路上还有另外一件事
But there is one other thing
that exist on this line one,
这里有一个从这里到这里的联系
which is that there is a linkage
from here back to here,
有一个属性指向，一个也叫做构造函数。
there is a property pointing back, and
that one is also called constructor.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 再一次，这只是为了假装
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And again, that exist
only for the purpose of trying to pretend
对你来说，那个物体是由工作坊的功能产生的，
to you that, that object was
created by the workshop function,
就像工作室函数是类的构造函数一样。
as if the workshop function
is a constructor for classes.
还有一个最后的东西存在一个隐藏的关系
And one final thing that exists,
there is a hidden relationship
在此对象与此对象之间。
between this object and this object.
如果我能用一条点线就能做到
I'm gonna do it, if I can,
with a dotted line.
这两者之间有着隐藏的关系
There's a hidden relationship
between those two.
我们待会儿再联系
We'll come back to that
relationship later.
但这都是第一行的结果
But all that's a result of line one.
你跟踪我吗
You follow me?
好了我们走第四线
All right, let's move to line four.
我们稍后再回来
We'll come back to two later.
我们走第四行
Let's move to line four.
在第四行，我们创建属性并将其添加到 workshop.prototype。
On line four, we make a property and
add it to workshop.prototype.
这并不重要，因为它是这个案件的功能。
It doesn't matter that it's
a function at this case.
所以我要把它写好
So I'm just gonna literally write it in.
我们只是在添加一个被称为直接询问这个对象的属性。
We're just adding a property called
ask directly to this object.
你和我一起吗
You with me?
第四行就是这样
That's what line four does.
我们要跳八行
We'll skip down to line eight.
这才是真正有趣的。
That's what's really interesting.
我想看如果你想拉上一张幻灯片
And I wanna review,
if you wanna pull up a slide or
翻到你的幻灯片里有 4 件事情发生在
flip back in your slides, there were
four things that happened whenever
新的运营商被放在一个功能调用的前面，就在第 8 行上。
the new operator was put in front of a
function call the way it is on line eight.
现在我们想做这四种事情，我要把它们每个都做个图表。
Now we want to do those four things and
I'm gonna diagram each one of them.
第一，第一件事发生在新事物的前方
So number one, the first thing that
happens when new is put in front of
函数调用是它在瘦空气中创建全新的空对象。
a function call is that it creates
a brand new empty object out of thin air.
这是我的全新的空物体。
So here is my brand new empty
object out of thin air.
然后它将该对象链接到另一个对象。
And then it links that
object to another object.
所以我要跟你联系
So here I'm gonna do a linkage,
与点线的隐藏联系
this little hidden linkage
with the dotted line.
它将该对象链接到另一个对象。
It links that object to another object.
第三个
Number three.
它调用它在前面调用的函数。
It invokes the function that
it was called in front of.
它调用此关键字指向对象。
It invokes that with the this
keyword pointing at the object.
所以现在我要搬去第二线了
So here we are, now,
I'm gonna move to line two, and
这个关键字指向这个特定对象，它是干什么的 ?
the this keyword is pointing at this
particular object, and what does it do?
加上一个叫老师的，所以我们要把老师
It adds a property called teacher,
so we're gonna put teacher
直接把它放在这里我就用它来缩写
directly right here on it, and
I'm just gonna abbreviate that with t-e-a.
我们把老师直接放在那个对象上。
We put teacher directly on that object.
这就是第二行
That's what line two does.
每个人都跟踪我吗
Everybody following me?
现在这个新关键词的第四个也是最后一个，当它回来的时候，
Now the fourth and final that the new
keyword does, when it returns it back,
如果该函数不返回对象，那么在此情况下它不返回。
if the function does not return an object,
which in this case it does not,
新关键字假定您打算返回到此关键字，即
the new keyword assumes that you meant to
return to the this keyword, that brand
新创建的对象，使其返回并获取名为 deepJS的名称。
new created object so that's get
returned back and it gets named deepJS.
因此，此对象称为 deepJS。
So this object is called deepJS.
我会叫它深的
I'll call it deep.
这就是第 8 行的情况如果你能理解
That's what happened with line eight and
if you understand what happened with line
八条一模一样的事发生在第九行
eight the exact same thing
happens with line nine.
所以我就把它画了
So I'll simply draw it in.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 我的绘画越来越差。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: My drawing
is getting much worse.
然后把老师的财产加给它然后它又回来了
And then it gets the teacher property
added on to it and it comes back and
这件案子是反动分子的
it's called in this case reactJS.
所以我只对反动分子说 R - e
So I'll just say R-e for reactJS.
那是第九行的对象
That's that object from line nine.
每个人都知道这些实体是从哪里来的
Everybody understand where these
entities are coming from and
他们的关系是什么
what their relationships are?
好，让我们来看第 11 行。
Okay, so let's look at line 11.
在该代码片段的第 11 行，我们说 deepJS.ask。
On line 11 of that code snippet,
we say deepJS.ask.
deepJS 对象，此对象在此处，是否具有请求方法?
Does the deepJS object, this object
right here, does it have an ask method?
没有。
It does not.
那么为什么我们可以称之为 " 方法 " 呢 ?
So why is it that we're
able to call that method?
因为我们的心理模式
Because our mental model if we were
thinking about these as classes
即会将该请求方法复制到该实例，但它不在该实例中。
is that the ask method would have been
copied to the instance but it isn't there.
相反，会发生的是内部联系，叫做
Instead, what is gonna happen is that
internal linkage, which is called
原型链，在 Speck ，它们使用支架，支架原型。
the prototype chain, in Speck,
they use bracket, bracket prototype.
它叫做原型链，内部就有一个链接。
It's called the prototype chain, and
so internally there's a linkage from
就在这个物体上的深处
the deep object, this one right here,
up to this object.
所以当我们寻找一个物体上的
So when we look for
a property on an object and
它不存在，缺省情况下，我们所做的做是做的。
it doesn't exist, by default,
what we do is do do do do do do do.
我们向链条上的下一个物体
We walk up one level to the next
object in the chain and
我们会问它是否有这一特性
we ask if it has that property.
在这件案子里是这样
Which in this case, it does.
它有一个要求的方法。
It has an ask method.
当我们援引第 5 行的提问方法时
When we invoke the ask method,
which was line five essentially,
这个关键词是什么意思
what is the this keyword gonna point at?
此关键字要指向哪个对象 ?
Which object is the this
keyword gonna point at?
它会指向这个物体
It's gonna point at this object.
为甚么呢 ?
Why?
因为呼叫站点是第 11 行。
Because the call site is line 11.
调用站点在 deepJS 上下文中调用该函数。
The call site says invoke that
function in the context of deepJS.
我们从哪里找到它的功能并不重要。
It doesn't matter where we
find the function from.
在这种情况下，我们发现了它的原型链，但这并不重要。
In this case, we found it up the prototype
chain, but it doesn't matter,
我们还是用这个调用点来调用它。
we still use the call site to invoke it.
你没有习惯用 JavaScript 的管道来思考这个问题。
You're not used to generally thinking this
deep about the plumbing of JavaScript.
但我认为这很重要，关键是你没有不正确的思维模式。
But I think it's important, critical that
you not have incorrect models of thinking.
好吧好吧 如果我们能用 deepJS 说的话
All right.
So if we can say that with deepJS,
我们也可以用反应对象说
we can also say that
with the react object.
当我们说的时候，第 14 行的反应对象会发生同样的事情。
The react object on line 14 when we say
.ask, the exact same thing happens.
我们没有一个问题的方法，但我们确实做了。
We don't have an ask method but
we go do do do do do do.
我们在调用的时候发现了这个方法，就是这个关键词指我们
We find the ask method when it is invoked,
it's this keyword is pointing out our
对象，那么当它说这个.师资时，它是在访问哪个属性 ?
object so when it says this .teacher
which property is it accessing?
就在这儿
This one right here.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 太好了吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: That's awesome right?
我们可以共享一个方法可能有无限数量的
We're able to share one method with
potentially an infinite number of
这些实例和它们都能够共享它，因为这种绑定行为和
instances and they're all able to share it
because of the this binding behavior and
原型链接。
that prototype linkage.
它其实是一个非常棒的系统。
It's actually a really awesome system.
我不是说这个样机
I'm not at all saying
that the prototype or
这个关键词系统不好，我只是说可能也有点
the this keyword system is bad, I'm
only saying that maybe it's a little too
限制只通过班级的镜头来思考这个问题
limiting to try to think about this
only through the lens of classes.
也许这个系统实际上比分类设计模式大得多。
Maybe the system is actually much more
powerful than the class design pattern.
如果切换到下一个幻灯片，您将看到建筑物的图。
If you switch to your next slide you'll
see the diagram of the buildings.
现在我要切换回幻灯片了
And I'm gonna switch back
to the slides now, so
如果你想把它复制下来或者把它复制下来就好了我的小画图
if you wanna copy this down or not copy it
down that's okay, my little bad drawing.
但现在至少你知道其中一些基本行为正在发生
But now at least you understand where some
of those fundamental behaviors are coming
啊，这些关系都是来的。
from, those relationships are coming from.